Nevada Folklife Archive
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
Nevada Folklife Archive 1980-2017
AFC 2017/002
Nevada Arts Council. Folklife Program
approximately 84,117 items
124 containers
approximately 119.8 linear feet
2.8 linear feet
9 oversize posters
294 text files: digital; pdf, doc
30 sound tape reels: analog; 7 in.
461 sound cassettes: analog
9,805 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
22,880 color transparencies; 35 mm
413 photographs: contact sheets, black and white; various sizes
26 photographs: prints, color; 4x6 in.
47,749 image files: digital; jpg, tif
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
This collection consists of photographs, recordings, and field notes documenting diverse culture, traditions, and communities in Nevada. Sponsored by the Nevada Arts Council Folklife Program, collection materials were collected by staff folklorists beginning in 1985.
Provenance
Nevada Arts Council, Folklife Program; 2016 and 2022.
Accruals
No further accruals are expected.
Access and Restrictions
The Nevada Folklife Archive is open to research. To request materials, please contact the Folklife Reading Room at https://hdl.loc.gov/loc.afc/folklife.contact
Certain restrictions to use or copying of materials may apply.
Administrative History
The Nevada Arts Council Folklife Program, a division of the Nevada Department of Tourism and Cultural Affairs, was founded in 1985. The organization administers grants, produces exhibits and publications, and initiates documentation projects that focus on the many forms of individual, organizational, and community folklife across the state of Nevada. The Nevada Folklife Archive existed as a repository for the fieldwork conducted by folklorists and contractors employed by the agency beginning in 1985. Folklorists employed by the Nevada Arts Council Folklife Program include Andrea Graham, Russell Frank, Blanton Owen, Eliza Buck, Jeanne Harrah Johnson, Anne F. Hatch, Michael Luster, Lesley Williams, Nicholas Curchin Vrooman, Tamara Layman, Debbie Nolan, Penny Rucks, and Christina Barr, among others.
Scope and Content
The Nevada Folklife Archive spans the years 1980 to 2017. The collection consists of field work conducted by folklorists employed by the Nevada Arts Council Folklife Program to document diverse communities and traditions across the state of Nevada.
Tasked with documenting various aspects of life and culture in Nevada, folklorists employed by the Nevada Arts Council Folklife Program collected the extensive sound recordings, photographs, transcripts, and field notes retained in this collection. The collection includes documentation of occupational folklife, including ranching, mining, railroad work, nuclear plants, and the entertainment industry; expressive traditions, including fiddling contests, cowboy poetry, leatherwork, glassblowing, basketry, quilting, music, and dance; and examples of vernacular architecture on ranches. Interviews and documentation highlight African American, Mormon, Paiute, Shoshone, Basque, Latinx, Japanese American, Thai American, South Asian American, Scottish American, and Italian American communities and traditions across Nevada. A large portion of the collection also documents programs and events sponsored by the Nevada Arts Council Folklife Program, including the Las Vegas Folklife Festival, the Sierra Folklife Festival, and the Folk Arts Apprenticeship. In addition to field work documentation, the collection includes correspondence relating to the administration of the Folklife Program, publications from the Folklife Program, and program files relating to the production of the Las Vegas Folklife Festival and the Sierra Folklife Festival.
Arrangement
The Nevada Folklife Archive is organized in 3 series:
Series 1: Manuscript materials, 1980-2017
Series 2: Sound recordings, 1985-2005
Series 3: Photographs, 1985-2005
Digital materials are arranged into AIPs to mirror the arrangement of analog materials in the collection. Collection materials were accompanied by a metadata spreadsheet provided by the donor. Researchers may wish to consult this spreadsheet to find more detailed, item level description of both analog and digital materials in the collection. See NFA Spreadsheet.xlsx
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Barr, Christina L.; Frank, Russell; Graham, Andrea; Hatch, Anne F.; Luster, Michael; Owen, Blanton, 1945-1998; Rucks, Penny; Vrooman, Nicholas Curchin; Williams, Lesley
Organizations
Nevada Arts Council
Subjects
African Americans--Nevada--Interviews.; Animals--Nevada--Anecdotes.; Ballads, English--Nevada.; Basque Americans--Nevada--Interviews.; Cemeteries--Nevada.; Cowboys--Nevada--Interviews.; Entertainment industry--Nevada.; Fiddling--Competitions--Nevada.; Folk music--Nevada.; Folk songs, English--Nevada.; Folklore--Nevada.; Food habits--Nevada.; Gamblers--Language.; Glass blowing and working--Nevada.; Gold mines and mining--Nevada--Anecdotes.; Horses--Nevada.; Hunting--Nevada.; Japanese Americans--Nevada--Interviews.; Latter Day Saints--Nevada--Folklore.; Latter Day Saints--Nevada--Interviews.; Leather workers--Nevada--Interviews.; Legends--Nevada.; Mexican Americans--Nevada--Interviews.; Miners--Nevada--Interviews.; Musicians--Nevada--Interviews.; Navajo Indians--Nevada--Interviews.; Nuclear weapons--Nevada--Testing--Anecdotes.; Paiute Indians--Nevada--Interviews.; Pilots--Nevada--Interviews.; Primitive Baptists--Nevada.; Quilts--Nevada.; Railroads--Employees--Nevada.; Ranchers--Nevada--Interviews.; Ranches--Nevada.; Rodeos--Nevada.; Shoshoni Indians--Nevada--Interviews.; South Asian Americans--Nevada--Interviews.; Thai Americans--Nevada--Interviews.; Tungsten mines and mining--Nevada--Anecdotes.; Uranium mines and mining--Nevada--Anecdotes.; Washoe Indians--Interviews.; Wild horses--Nevada.
Places
Nevada--Social life and customs.
Form/Genre
Aerial photographs.; Cowboy poetry.; Dance music.; Field notes.; Interviews.; Manuscripts.; Oral histories.; Personal narratives.; Photographs.; Poems.; Songs.; Sound recordings.
Container List
- Series 1: Manuscript materials
  - Subseries 1: Field notes
    Scope and content: Field notes collected by folklorists documenting Nevada folklife in a variety of projects and surveys, including the Folklife Apprenticeship Program, the Lander County Survey, the Douglas County Survey, the Reno Folk Arts Survey, and the Las Vegas Folk Arts Survey.
    Arrangement: This subseries is arranged by the original Item ID number provided by the donor. The archivist retained folder headings provided by the donor and copied from documentation provided by the donor to create any additional description found in the finding aid. Description linking field notes to their associated audio and visual content has been provided wherever possible. This subseries contains both born digital and digitized files.
    - Site visit to Austin, Nevada for Gridley Days and the Old Time Fiddle Contest, June 13, 1986, P-1986-032 - P-1986-034, P-1986-052 - P-1986-056, C-1986-014, C-1986-016; Andrea Graham; F-1986-001; 13 pages; handwritten notes. (Box-folder 117/1)
    - Lander County Survey: from a two-week site visit to Austin and environs, March 23, 1988, P-1988-001, C-1988-004, C-1988-015, S-1988-003, S-1988-043; Andrea Graham; F-1988-001; 13 pages; typed notes with handwritten notes added. (Box-folder 117/2)
    - Lander County Survey: site visit to Battle Mountain, April 15, 1988, C-1988-019; Andrea Graham; F-1988-002; 13 pages; typed and handwritten notes.; Includes notes on site visit to Dan and Berdine Ramos at the Battle Mountain Indian Colony. (Box-folder 117/3)
    - Lander County Survey: site visit to Austin and environs, May 2, 1988, S-1988-083, P-1988-031; Andrea Graham; F-1988-003; 10 pages; typed and handwritten notes.; Includes site visit with Bernice Hooper, notes from tour of Kingston Mine and Battle Mountain Gold Mine. (Box-folder 117/4)
    - Lander County Survey, April 20, 1988, Andrea Graham; F-1988-004; 12 pages; handwritten notes.; Includes time sheets, contacts, bibliography and notes about the survey project and publication. (Box-folder 117/5)
    - Lander County Survey, March 7, 1988 - May 6, 1988, Andrea Graham; F-1988-005; 14 pages; handwritten notes; 1 map.; Includes notes from visit to cemetery; visit to the Daniels Hay Ranch in Smoky Valley (Nye County), notes from site visits, contacts and notes from meeting with local Chamber of Commerce. (Box-folder 117/6)
    - Douglas County Survey, June 22, 1989, Andrea Graham; F-1989-001; 12 pages; typed with handwritten notes; 24 pages handwritten notes.; Includes notes from site visit with Joann Martinez and members of the Cordes family; contacts and bibliography. (Box-folder 117/7)
    - FAA 1990: Site visit with Eddie Brooks, saddle maker at Elko, November 1990, Andrea Graham; F-1990-001; 2 pages; handwritten notes. (Box-folder 117/8)
    - Site visit to teacher in-service class at Carson City, presented by JoAnn Martinez of Gardnerville, October 22, 1990, Andrea Graham; F-1990-002; 2 pages; typed notes. (Box-folder 117/9)
    - FAA 1990: Site visit to Reno Indian Colony for teacher in-service presentation by Steve Kane, October 23, 1990, Andrea Graham; F-1990-003; 1 page; typed notes. (Box-folder 117/10)
    - Site visit to Wa-Pai-Shone Culture Day at Meleley Elementary School in Gardnerville for presentations by Florine Conway, JoAnn Martinez, Teresa Jackson, Norm DeLorme, and others, October 27, 1990, Andrea Graham; F-1990-004; 2 pages; typed with handwritten notes. (Box-folder 117/11)
    - FAA 1991: Site visit with Norma Williams and Stacy Gibbs, Paiute buckskin smoking, in Schurz, December 3, 1990, Andrea Graham; F-1990-005; 2 pages; handwritten notes. (Box-folder 117/12)
    - Las Vegas Cultural Survey: fieldnotes collected by Lesley Williams, November - December 1991, S-1991-102, S-1991-106 - S-1991-108, S-1991-110 - S-1991-117, P-1991-003, P-1991-013 - P-1991-015, C-1991-013, C-1991-015 - C-1991-016, C-1991-021 - C-1991-022, C-1991-027; Lesley Williams; F-1991-001 - F-1991-030; 3 pages; typed notes. (Box-folder 117/13)
    - Las Vegas Cultural Survey: field notes collected by Russell Frank, October 30, 1991 - December 15, 1991, Russell Frank; F-1991-031 - F-1991-032-42; 2 pages; typed notes. (Box-folder 117/14)
    - Teresa Jackson and Norrine Smokey-Smith, Washoe basketmaking, Folklife Apprenticeship Grant site visit interview, March 20, 1991, Andrea Graham; F-1991-033; 2 pages; typed notes. (Box-folder 117/15)
    - Angie McGarva and Tammi Knight, Shoshone beadwork, Folklife Apprenticeship Grant site visit interview, August 30, 1991, C-1991-005 - C-1991-006, S-1992-004 - S-1992-005, P-1992-005; Andrea Graham; F-1991-034; 5 pages; typed notes. (Box-folder 117/16)
    - Brenda Hooper and Jeanette Losh, Shoshone basketry, Folklife Apprenticeship Grant site visit interview, September 1, 1991, S-1992-006, P-1992-002; Andrea Graham; F-1991-035; 3 pages; typed notes. (Box-folder 117/17)
    - Norm and Bernie DeLorme, Native American beadwork and basketry, Folklife Apprenticeship Grant site visit interview, December 20, 1991, Andrea Graham; F-1991-036; 2 pages; typed notes. (Box-folder 117/18)
    - Thailand Nevada Association, July 29, 1992, Andrea Graham; F-1992-001; 4 pages; typed notes. (Box-folder 117/19)
    - Dean Barlese and Heidi Barlese, powwow drumming and singing, Folklife Apprenticeship Grant site visit interview, September 16, 1992, S-1992-020, P-1992-006; Andrea Graham; F-1992-002; 3 pages; typed notes; 1 newspaper article. (Box-folder 117/20)
    - Adam Fortunate Eagle, stone pipestem carving, Folklife Apprenticeship Grant site visit interview, September 23, 1992, S-1992-020, P-1992-006; Andrea Graham; F-1992-003; 3 pages; typed notes. (Box-folder 117/21)
    - Dinane Ohata-Sims, Hawaiian gourd art, Folklife Apprenticeship Grant site visit interview, July 29, 1992, C-1992-008 - C-1992-009, P-1992-009 - P-1992-010; Andrea Graham; F-1992-004; 2 pages; typed notes.; Includes proposal to name cultural facility for Rafael Rivera. (Box-folder 117/22)
    - Zoria Zetaruk and Natalie Pruc, Ukrainian egg art (pysanky), Folklife Apprenticeship Grant site visit interview, September 12, 1993, C-1993-010, P-1993-030; Andrea Graham; F-1993-001; 2 pages; typed notes.; Includes 1 restaurant menu. (Box-folder 117/23)
    - Pat Kanoknata and Santhana Lopez, Thai Classical Dance, Folklife Apprenticeship Grant site visit interview, September 12, 1993, S-1993-044, P-1993-027; Andrea Graham; F-1993-002; 3 pages; typed notes. (Box-folder 117/24)
    - Amy Barber and Jody Barber Steele, Washoe basketry, Folklife Apprenticeship Grant site visit interview, August 26, 1993, S-1993-045, P-1993-027; Andrea Graham; F-1993-003; 2 pages; typed notes. (Box-folder 117/25)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey (Eliza Buck); Reno area folk artists and contact people, October 2, 1994 - October 17, 1994, Eliza Buck; F-1994-001; 2 pages; typed notes; 4 page brochure.; Photo opportunities and other contact dates; list of folk art forms represented in survey. (Box-folder 117/26)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey: Lisa Cocostegui, phone interview, October 1, 1994, Eliza Buck; F-1994-002; 3 pages; typed notes.; Includes an artist biography for Ella Bell and a copy of a newspaper article. (Box-folder 117/27)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey: Jesse Hall, Interfaith Gospel Choir, October 3, 1994, C-1994-007 - C-1994-008, P-1994-011, S-1994-023 - S-1994-024; Eliza Buck; F-1994-003; 2 pages; typed notes. (Box-folder 117/28)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey: Truckee River Travels, Native American drum and dance corps, October 2, 1994, P-1994-010, S-1994-021 - S-1994-022; Eliza Buck; F-1994-004; 2 pages; typed notes. (Box-folder 117/29)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey: Vassili Titus, The Aegean Sea, traditional Greek music, October 3, 1994, Eliza Buck; F-1994-005; 4 pages; typed notes.; Includes 1 menu for N'Orleans Restaurant and 1 Las Vegas Cultural Tour flyer. (Box-folder 117/30)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey: Vinny Ribas, entertainment industry, October 3, 1994, Eliza Buck; F-1994-006; 2 pages; typed notes. (Box-folder 117/31)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey: Dr. Greg "Lightning" Williams, auctioneering, October 3, 1994, C-1994-014, S-1994-030, P-1994-014; Eliza Buck; F-1994-007; 2 pages; typed notes. (Box-folder 118/1)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey: Dan Price, silversmith, October 4, 1994, C-1994-009 - C-1994-010, S-1994-025, P-1994-010, P-1994-012; Eliza Buck; F-1994-008; 3 pages; typed notes. (Box-folder 118/2)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey: Wade's Silver Shop, October 8, 1994, P-1994-010, S-1994-025; Eliza Buck; F-1994-009; 1 page; typed notes. (Box-folder 118/3)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey: Gujurati Community of Reno, Navratri festival, October 8, 1994, P-1994-010, P-1994-016 - P-1994-017, S-1994-033; Eliza Buck; F-1994-010; 2 pages; typed notes. (Box-folder 118/4)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey: H.B. McCay, farrier, October 10, 1994, P-1994-010, P-1994-018, C-1994-017 - C-1994-018, S-1994-034 - S-1994-035; Eliza Buck; F-1994-011; 2 pages; typed notes. (Box-folder 118/5)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey: Martin Lane, newspaperman, October 11, 1994, Eliza Buck; F-1994-012; 1 page; typed notes.; Includes order form for Noveau Navajo. (Box-folder 118/6)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey: Carl Kuttle, storyteller, October 11, 1994, Eliza Buck; F-1994-013; 4 pages; typed notes.; Includes description of the hoop dance. (Box-folder 118/7)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey: Red Watson, storyteller, October 11, 1994, Eliza Buck; F-1994-014; 1 page; typed notes. (Box-folder 118/8)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey: Manuel Ramirez Hernandez, Mexican folkloric dance, October 12, 1994, P-1994-010, C-1994-022, S-1994-038 - S-1994-039; Eliza Buck; F-1994-015; 1 page; typed notes.; Includes Japanese calligraphy; photocopies of Lance Burton photographs; a JKT Tour and Gifts order form; and a Vegas Hawaii Tour brochure. (Box-folder 118/9)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey: Manuel Ramirez Hernandez, traditional Mexican music, October 12, 1994, Eliza Buck; F-1994-016; 2 pages; typed notes.; Includes class list and flyer for Simba Talent Development Center. (Box-folder 118/10)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey: Tongan Methodist church community and choir, October 12, 1994, C-1994-005 - C-1994-006, C-1994-019, P-1994-019, S-1994-037 - S-1994-038; Eliza Buck; F-1994-017; 2 pages; typed notes. (Box-folder 118/11)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey: Colin Sendall, dowsing, October 12, 1994, C-1994-020, P-1994-020, S-1994-037; Eliza Buck; F-1994-018; 1 folder (Box-folder 118/12)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey: Arun Sachdev, India Association of Northern Nevada, October 14, 1994, P-1994-021 - P-1994-022, S-1994-039; Eliza Buck; F-1994-019; 4 pages; handwritten index; 56 pages; typed notes; 20 pages; handwritten informant sheets. (Box-folder 118/13)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey: Balhi Saihi, India Association of Northern Nevada, October 14, 1994, Eliza Buck; F-1994-020; 1 folder (Box-folder 118/14)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey: Karen Burns, showgirl, October 14, 1994, C-1994-023 - C-1994-024, P-1994-022, S-1994-039; Eliza Buck; F-1994-021; 1 folder (Box-folder 118/15)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey: Norm and Bernie DeLorme, beadwork and basketry, Native American, October 16, 1994, C-1994-026 - C-1994-027, P-1994-023, S-1994-041 - S-1994-042; Eliza Buck; F-1994-022; 1 folder (Box-folder 118/16)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey: Tariq Qureshi, Farida, Pakistani Association of Nevada, October 16, 1994, Eliza Buck; F-1994-023; 1 folder (Box-folder 118/17)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey: Looney Bin Clown Alley, clowning, October 4, 1994, Eliza Buck; F-1994-024; 1 folder (Box-folder 118/18)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey: Don Brandfas, Terry Wilson, The Magic Shop, October 5, 1994, C-1994-011 - C-1994-012, P-1994-013, S-1994-026; Eliza Buck; F-1994-025; 1 folder (Box-folder 118/19)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey: Visha Siddharthan, Diwali Festival, October 6, 1994, C-1994-011 - C-1994-012, S-1994-027 - S-1994-028; Eliza Buck; F-1994-026; 1 folder (Box-folder 118/20)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey: Fieldwork update by Tamara Layman, November 1994, Tamara Layman; F-1994-027; 1 folder (Box-folder 118/21)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey update: Diwali Celebration Festival of Lights, Billinghurst Middle School, November 5, 1994, C-1994-030, S-1994-047 - S-1994-048; Tamara Layman; F-1994-028; 1 folder (Box-folder 118/22)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey update: Second Baptist Church service, November 5, 1994, C-1994-031 - C-1994-032, S-1994-047 - S-1994-048; Tamara Layman; F-1994-029; 1 folder (Box-folder 118/23)
    - Reno Folk Arts Survey update: Celtic New Year celebration, November 4, 1994 - November 6, 1994, S-1994-044 - S-1994-046; Tamara Layman; F-1994-030; 1 folder (Box-folder 118/24)
    - David Johnson and David McDonald, D Bar J Hat Company, Folklife Apprenticeship Grant site visit interview, February 10, 1994, P-1994-001 - P-1994-003; Andrea Graham; F-1994-031; 1 folder (Box-folder 118/25)
    - Clara Castillo and Jessica Lake, Northern Paiute willow basketmaking, Folklife Apprenticeship Grant site visit interview, December 10, 1995, P-1995-020, S-1995-053 - S-1995-054; Andrea Graham; F-1995-001; 1 folder (Box-folder 118/26)
    - Amy Rovere, Filipino dance, Folklife Apprenticeship Grant site visit interview, September 21, 1995, P-1995-015 - P-1995-016, S-1995-043; Andrea Graham; F-1995-002; 1 folder (Box-folder 118/27)
    - Wanthanee Natechoei and Pannee Connoly interview, Thai dance, Folklife Apprenticeship Grant site visit interview, October 24, 1995, P-1995-017, S-1995-045; Andrea Graham; F-1995-003; 1 folder (Box-folder 118/28)
    - Mary and Frank Esparza, site visit. Mary makes cascarones, pinatas and cooks Mexican food, March 20, 1995, Andrea Graham; F-1995-004; 1 folder (Box-folder 118/29)
    - Melanie Bryan, Jeanne O'Daye, Jeanne McNicoll with Head Start kids from Hungry Valley on picnic and sharing traditional knowledge about basketry and other things, November 13, 1996, C-1997-011, P-1996-012, P-1996-019, S-1996-039 - S-1996-040; Andrea Graham; F-1996-001; 1 folder (Box-folder 118/30)
    - Robin Williams Burgoyne, interview and site visit, talking about Dooby Avenue in Gerlach and her father DeWayne Arthur "Dooby" Williams, July 13, 1996, P-1996-012; Andrea Graham; F-1996-002; 1 folder (Box-folder 118/31)
    - Las Vegas Folk Arts Survey (Eliza Buck): Survey undertaken to identify folk artists/cultural groups to participate in the Las Vegas Folklife Festival, May 1997 - April 1998, Eliza Buck; F-1998-001; 1 folder (Box-folder 118/32)
    - Great Basin Tribal Gathering, July 9 - July 12, 1998, P-1998-016 - P-1998-018, S-1998-035 - S-1998-038; Andrea Graham; F-1998-002; 1 folder; Notes, reports, correspondence, evaluation, and ephemera relating to the planning and implementation of The Great Basin Tribal Gathering on South Fork Reservation in Lee, Nevada. (Box-folder 118/33)
    - Firouzeh Forouzmand interview, Iranian wedding traditions, June 13, 1998, Jeanne Johnson; F-1998-003; 1 folder (Box-folder 118/34)
    - Firouzeh Forouzmand interview, Iranian wedding traditions, June 4, 1998, Jeanne Johnson; F-1998-004; 1 folder (Box-folder 118/35)
    - Nancy Williams Baker interview, August 27, 2002, C-2003-026 - C-2003-027, S-2003-028 - S-2003-031; Christina Barr; F-2002-001; 1 folder (Box-folder 118/36)
    - Girtia Lukes interview, June 15, 2004, C-2004-008, S-2004-017; Anne F. Hatch; F-2004-001; 1 folder (Box-folder 118/37)
    - Notes on the World Flair Bartending Championship Finals, April 1, 2004, afc2017002_series1; F-2004-002; 1 text file (.doc)
    - Notes on Jewish Independence Day observance at the Bellagio, May 2, 2004, afc2017002_series1; Anne F. Hatch; F-2004-003; 1 text file (.doc)
    - Notes from interview with Elaine Smokey and Norberta Whistler on Folk Arts Apprenticeship project in basket making, September 23, 2003, afc2017002_series1; Jeanne Johnson; F-2004-004; 1 text file (.doc)
    - Linda Johnson-Comas interview, July 13, 2005, S-2005-008; Anne F. Hatch; F-2005-001 (Box-folder 118/38)
    - Notes from site visit to procession celebrating Our Lady of Guadalupe, December 11, 2004, afc2017002_series1; Anne F. Hatch; F-2005-002; 1 text file (.doc)
    - Notes from site visit with Daniel Ramos about basketweaving, January 26, 2005, afc2017002_series1; Anne F. Hatch; F-2005-003; 1 text file (.doc)
    - Notes from site visit to the Rainbow Library for a Scottish Heritage exhibit, January 21, 2005, afc2017002_series1; Anne F. Hatch; F-2005-004; 1 text file (.doc)
    - Nevada aeronautical chart used by Blanton Owen, undated, 1 folder (Box-folder 118/39)
  - Subseries 2: Collection documentation
    Scope and content: Logs containing item level information about audio and visual content contained in the collection.
    Arrangement: This subseries is arranged by type of log and chronologically therein. This subseries contains both digitized and born digital materials.
    - Cassette logs, 1986, 1 folder (Box-folder 118/40)
    - Cassette logs, 1987, 1 folder (Box-folder 118/41)
    - Cassette logs, 1988, 1 folder (Box-folder 118/42)
    - Cassette logs, 1989, 1 folder (Box-folder 119/1)
    - Cassette logs, 1990, 1 folder (Box-folder 119/2)
    - Cassette logs, 1991-1998, afc2017002_series1; 10 text files (.pdf)
    - Recording logs, 2017, afc2017002_series1; 9 text files (.doc)
    - Reel-to-reel logs (1 of 2), 1987, 1 folder (Box-folder 119/3)
    - Reel-to-reel logs (2 of 2), 1987, 1 folder (Box-folder 119/4)
    - Slide logs, 1980, afc2017002_series1; 1 text file (.pdf)
    - Slide logs, 1986, 1 folder (Box-folder 119/5)
    - Slide logs (1 of 2), 1987, 1 folder (Box-folder 119/6)
    - Slide logs (2 of 2), 1987, 1 folder (Box-folder 119/7)